<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ReadBooks</string>
    <string name="your_library">Моя библиотека</string>

    <string name="book1">Смерть ловит рыбу. Веселится на вечеринке. Напивается в трактире. А все обязанности Мрачного Жнеца сваливаются на хрупкие плечи его ученика. Но делать нечего: берем косу, прыгаем на белую лошадь Бинки — и вперед!</string>
    <string name="book2">«Мастер и Маргарита» - роман, воплотивший размышления М.А. Булгакова о современности и вечности человека и мира, художника и власти, — роман, в котором удивительным образом переплетаются едкая сатира, тонкий психологический анализ и философское обобщение.</string>
    <string name="book3">Сборник рассказов, объединенных общей темой — историей освоения Марса людьми, судьбой прежних жителей планеты, а главное — судьбами простых людей, оказавшихся в непростых ситуациях.</string>
    <string name="book4">Крестный отец» — классический роман о жизни одного из могущественных преступных синдикатов Америки — мафиозном клане дона Корлеоне. Написанная с потрясающей достоверностью книга позволяет читателю без риска для жизни заглянуть в святая святых Мафии</string>
    <string name="book5">Секретный код скрыт в работах Леонардо да Винчи…Только он поможет найти христианские святыни, дававшие немыслимые власть и могущество…Ключ к величайшей тайне, над которой человечество билось веками, наконец может быть найден…</string>
    <string name="book6">An ancient secret brotherhood. A devastating new weapon of destruction. An unthinkable target. When world-renowned Harvard symbologist Robert Langdon is summoned to his first assignment to a Swiss research facility to analyze a mysterious symbol &#8212; seared into the chest of a murdered physicist &#8212; he discovers evidence of the unimaginable: the resurgence of an ancient secret brotherhood known as the Illuminati&#8230;the most powerful underground organization ever to walk the earth. The Illuminati has now surfaced to carry out the final phase of its legendary vendetta against its most hated enemy &#8212; the Catholic Church. </string>
    <string name="book7">This laugh-out-loud chronicle charts a year in the life of Bridget Jones, a single girl on a permanent, doomed quest for self-improvement &#8212;in which she resolves to: visit the gym three times a week not merely to buy a sandwich, form a functional relationship with a responsible adult, and not fall for any of the following: misogynists, megalomaniacs, adulterers, workaholics, chauvinists or perverts. And learn to program the VCR. Caught between her Singleton friends, who are all convinced they will end up dying alone and found three weeks later half-eaten by an Alsatian, and the Smug Marrieds, whose dinner parties offer ever-new opportunities for humiliation, Bridget struggles to keep her life on an even keel (or at least afloat). Through it all, she will have her readers helpless with laughter and shouting, "BRIDGET JONES IS ME!"</string>
    <string name="book8">When a new NASA satellite spots evidence of an astonishingly rare object buried deep in the Arctic ice, the floundering space agency proclaims a much-needed victory&#8230;a victory that has profound implications for U.S. space policy and the impending presidential election. With the Oval Office in the balance, the President dispatches White House Intelligence analyst Rachel Sexton to the Milne Ice Shelf to verify the authenticity of the find. Accompanied by a team of experts, including the charismatic academic Michael Tolland, Rachel uncovers the unthinkable: evidence of scientific trickery &#8212; a bold deception that threatens to plunge the world into controversy.</string>
    <string name="book9">America’s preeminent storyteller, imagines a place of hope, dreams, and metaphor— of crystal pillars and fossil seas—where a fine dust settles on the great empty cities of a vanished, devastated civilization. Earthmen conquer Mars and then are conquered by it, lulled by dangerous lies of comfort and familiarity, and enchanted by the lingering glamour of an ancient, mysterious native race. In this classic work of fiction, Bradbury exposes our ambitions, weaknesses, and ignorance in a strange and breathtaking world where man does not belong.</string>
    <string name="book10">Jack Torrance’s new job at the Overlook Hotel is the perfect chance for a fresh start. As the off-season caretaker at the atmospheric old hotel, he’ll have plenty of time to spend reconnecting with his family and working on his writing. But as the harsh winter weather sets in, the idyllic location feels ever more remote&#8230;and more sinister. And the only one to notice the strange and terrible forces gathering around the Overlook is Danny Torrance, a uniquely gifted five-year-old.</string>
    <string name="book11">There are more than 101 things to love about Disney’s 101 Dalmatians! The animated classic from 1961 is being released in a Platinum Edition DVD, so a whole new generation of children will come to love Perdita and Pongo, Cruella DeVil, and all those adorable puppies. This Little Golden Book retells all the tail-wagging excitement of the film.</string>
    <string name="book12">In this celebrated work, his only novel, Wilde forged a devastating portrait of the effects of evil and debauchery on a young aesthete in late-19th-century England. Combining elements of the Gothic horror novel and decadent French fiction, the book centers on a striking premise.</string>
    <string name="book13">Speaking to us with the wisdom of age and in a voice at once haunting and startlingly immediate, Nitta Sayuri tells the story of her life as a geisha. It begins in a poor fishing village in 1929, when, as a nine-year-old girl with unusual blue-gray eyes, she is taken from her home and sold into slavery to a renowned geisha house. We witness her transformation as she learns the rigorous arts of the geisha: dance and music; wearing kimono, elaborate makeup, and hair. </string>
    <string name="book14">The War of the Worlds has two parts, Book One: The Coming of the Martians and Book Two: The Earth under the Martians. The narrator, a philosophically inclined author, struggles to return to his wife while seeing the Martians lay waste to the southern country outside London. Book One also imparts the experience of his brother, also unnamed, who describes events as they deteriorate in the capital, forcing him to escape the Martian onslaught by boarding a paddle steamer near Tillingham, on the Essex coast.</string>
    <string name="book15">The story of the creation of the world and of the First Age, this is the ancient drama to which the characters in The Lord of the Rings look back and in whose events some of them, such as Elrond and Galadriel, took part. The three Silmarils were jewels created by Fëanor, most gifted of the Elves. Within them was imprisoned the Light of the Two Trees of Valinor before the Trees themselves were destroyed by Morgoth, the first Dark Lord. Thereafter, the unsullied Light of Valinor lived on only in the Silmarils, but they were seized by Morgoth and set in his crown, which was guarded in the impenetrable fortress of Angband in the north of Middle-earth.</string>
    <string name="book16">Guy Montag is a fireman. In his world, where television rules and literature is on the brink of extinction, firemen start fires rather than put them out. His job is to destroy the most illegal of commodities, the printed book, along with the houses in which they are hidden.</string>
    <string name="book17"> University of Oxford Marianne Dashwood wears her heart on her sleeve, and when she falls in love with the dashing but unsuitable John Willoughby she ignores her sister Elinor warning that her impulsive behaviour leaves her open to gossip and innuendo. Meanwhile Elinor, always sensitive to social convention, is struggling to conceal her own romantic disappointment, even from those closest to her. Through their parallel experience of love - and its threatened loss - the sisters learn that sense must mix with sensibility if they are to find personal happiness in a society where status and money govern the rules of love. </string>
    <string name="book18">Welcome to Cold Mountain Penitentiary, home to the Depression-worn men of E Block. Convicted killers all, each awaits his turn to walk the Green Mile, keeping a date with “Old Sparky,” Cold Mountain’s electric chair. Prison guard Paul Edgecombe has seen his share of oddities in his years working the Mile. But he’s never seen anyone like John Coffey, a man with the body of a giant and the mind of a child, condemned for a crime terrifying in its violence and shocking in its depravity. In this place of ultimate retribution, Edgecombe is about to discover the terrible, wondrous truth about Coffey, a truth that will challenge his most cherished beliefs&#8230;and yours.</string>
    <string name="book19">In ancient times the Rings of Power were crafted by the Elven-smiths, and Sauron, the Dark Lord, forged the One Ring, filling it with his own power so that he could rule all others. But the One Ring was taken from him, and though he sought it throughout Middle-earth, it remained lost to him. After many ages it fell into the hands of Bilbo Baggins, as told in The Hobbit. In a sleepy village in the Shire, young Frodo Baggins finds himself faced with an immense task, as his elderly cousin Bilbo entrusts the Ring to his care. Frodo must leave his home and make a perilous journey across Middle-earth to the Cracks of Doom, there to destroy the Ring and foil the Dark Lord in his evil purpose.</string>
    <string name="book20">The unforgettable novel of a childhood in a sleepy Southern town and the crisis of conscience that rocked it, To Kill A Mockingbird became both an instant bestseller and a critical success when it was first published in 1960. It went on to win the Pulitzer Prize in 1961 and was later made into an Academy Award-winning film, also a classic.</string>
    <string name="book21">Until the day a small band of nomes arrives at the Store from the Outside. Led by a young nome named Masklin, the Outsiders carry a mysterious black box (called the Thing), and they deliver devastating news: In twenty-one days, the Store will be destroyed.</string>
    <string name="book22">The Color of Magic is Terry Pratchett maiden voyage through the now-legendary land of Discworld. This is where it all begins &#8212; with the tourist Twoflower and his wizard guide, Rincewind.</string>
    <string name="book23">At thirty-one, Noah Calhoun, back in coastal North Carolina after World War II, is haunted by images of the girl he lost more than a decade earlier. At twenty-nine, socialite Allie Nelson is about to marry a wealthy lawyer, but she cannot stop thinking about the boy who long ago stole her heart. Thus begins the story of a love so enduring and deep it can turn tragedy into triumph, and may even have the power to create a miracle&#8230;</string>
    <string name="book24">When inept, but well-intentioned Mort gets only one offer for an apprenticeship—with Death—he can’t exactly turn it down. But Mort finds that being Death’s right-hand man isn’t as bad as it seems—until he falls back to his old, bumbling ways.</string>


    <string name="cover1">http://i.livelib.ru/boocover/1000161421/o/013e/Terri_Pratchett__Mor_uchenik_Smerti.jpeg</string>
    <string name="cover2">http://www.kniga.info/images/prod5/k_master_i_margarita_m.jpg</string>
    <string name="cover3">https://encrypted-tbn3.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcSynEh5IfojQGe06KazruP8GOisp7w5APpn1J4vh85l5T7LYx8i</string>
    <string name="cover4">http://sweetbook.net/uploads/topics/preview/00/00/04/90/06384982b4_200crop.jpg</string>
    <string name="cover5">http://static1.read.ru/covers_rr/b/40/95/3559540.jpg</string>
    <string name="cover6">http://images.amazon.com/images/P/0671027360.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</string>
    <string name="cover7">http://images.amazon.com/images/P/0330332775.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</string>
    <string name="cover8">http://images.amazon.com/images/P/0671027387.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</string>
    <string name="cover9">http://images.amazon.com/images/P/0380973839.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</string>
    <string name="cover10">http://images.amazon.com/images/P/0743424425.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</string>
    <string name="cover11">http://images.amazon.com/images/P/0307001164.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</string>
    <string name="cover12">http://images.amazon.com/images/P/0140620338.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</string>
    <string name="cover13">http://images.amazon.com/images/P/0099771519.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</string>
    <string name="cover14">http://images.amazon.com/images/P/0425050750.01.THUMBZZZ.jpg</string>
    <string name="cover15">http://images.amazon.com/images/P/0345325818.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</string>
    <string name="cover16">http://images.amazon.com/images/P/9505470010.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</string>
    <string name="cover17">http://images.amazon.com/images/P/0451187903.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</string>
    <string name="cover18">http://images.amazon.com/images/P/0671032658.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</string>
    <string name="cover19">http://images.amazon.com/images/P/0345339703.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</string>
    <string name="cover20">http://images.amazon.com/images/P/0446310492.01.THUMBZZZ.jpg</string>
    <string name="cover21">http://images.amazon.com/images/P/0385304366.01.THUMBZZZ.jpg</string>
    <string name="cover22">http://images.amazon.com/images/P/0061020710.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</string>
    <string name="cover23">http://images.amazon.com/images/P/0446605239.01.MZZZZZZZ.jpg</string>
    <string name="cover24">http://images.amazon.com/images/P/0451159233.01.THUMBZZZ.jpg</string>


    <string name="author1">Тэрри Пратчетт</string>
    <string name="author2">Михаил Булгаков</string>
    <string name="author3">Рэй Брэдбери</string>
    <string name="author4">Марио Пьюзо</string>
    <string name="author5">Дэн Браун</string>
    <string name="author6">Dan Brown</string>
    <string name="author7">Helen Fielding</string>
    <string name="author8">Dan Brown</string>
    <string name="author9">Ray Bradbury</string>
    <string name="author10">Stephen King</string>
    <string name="author11">Justine Korman</string>
    <string name="author12">Oscar Wilde</string>
    <string name="author13">Arthur Golden</string>
    <string name="author14">H. G. Wells</string>
    <string name="author15">J.R.R. Tolkien</string>
    <string name="author16">Ray Bradbury</string>
    <string name="author17">Jane Austen</string>
    <string name="author18">Stephen King</string>
    <string name="author19">J.R.R. Tolkien</string>
    <string name="author20">Harper Lee</string>
    <string name="author21">Terry Pratchett</string>
    <string name="author22">Terry Pratchett</string>
    <string name="author23">Nicholas Sparks</string>
    <string name="author24">Terry Pratchett</string>

    <string name="title1">Мор, ученик Смерти</string>
    <string name="title2">&quot;Мастер и Маргарита&quot;</string>
    <string name="title3">&quot;Марсианские хроники&quot;</string>
    <string name="title4">&quot;Крестный отец&quot;</string>
    <string name="title5">&quot;Код да Винчи&quot;</string>
    <string name="title6">&quot;Angels and Demons&quot;</string>
    <string name="title7">Bridget Jones Diary</string>
    <string name="title8">Deception Point</string>
    <string name="title9">Martian Chronicles</string>
    <string name="title10">The Shining</string>
    <string name="title11">101 Dalmatians</string>
    <string name="title12">Picture of Dorian Gray</string>
    <string name="title13">Memoirs of a Geisha</string>
    <string name="title14">War of the Worlds</string>
    <string name="title15">The Silmarillion</string>
    <string name="title16">Fahrenheit 451</string>
    <string name="title17">Sense and Sensibility</string>
    <string name="title18">The Green Mile</string>
    <string name="title19">The Fellowship of the Ring</string>
    <string name="title20">To Kill a Mockingbird</string>
    <string name="title21">Wings</string>
    <string name="title22">The Color of Magic</string>
    <string name="title23">The Notebook</string>
    <string name="title24">Mort</string>
</resources>
